valley.com 2019-06-26

# Privacy Policy Notice

                                                                                                     Privacy Policy Notice
                                                                                                                   Effective January, 2019
     FACTS            What does Valley National Bank (Valley) do with your personal information?
                      Financial companies choose how they share your personal information. Federal law gives consumers the right
      WHY?            to limit some but not all sharing. Federal law also requires us to tell you how we collect, share, and protect your
                      personal information. Please read this notice carefully to understand what we do.
                      The types of personal information we collect and share depend on the product or service you have with us. This
                      information can include:
     WHAT?            • Social Security Number and account balances
                      • Transaction history and income
                      • Assets and account transactions
                      All financial companies need to share customers’ personal information to run their everyday business. In the
      HOW?            section below, we list the reasons financial companies can share their customers’ personal information; the
                      reasons Valley chooses to share; and whether you can limit this sharing.
                                                                                                                          Can you limit
Reasons we can share your personal information                                             Does Valley share?
                                                                                                                          this sharing?
For our everyday business purposes — such as to process your transactions,
maintain your account(s), respond to court orders and legal investigations, or report               Yes                          No
to credit bureaus
For our marketing purposes — to offer our products and services to you                              Yes                          No
For joint marketing with other financial companies                                                  Yes                          No
For our affiliates’ everyday business purposes — information about your
                                                                                                    Yes                          No
transactions and experiences
For our affiliates’ everyday business purposes — information about your
                                                                                                    Yes                         Yes
creditworthiness
For our affiliates to market to you                                                                 Yes                         Yes
For non-affiliates to market to you                                                                 No                   We don’t share
                                      Call Customer Service at 800-522-4100 from 6 AM -11 PM ET, 7 days a week, email us at
                                      privacy@valley.com or write to:
                                      Valley National Bank
                                      Attention: Customer Service, Privacy Section
     To limit our sharing             1445 Valley Road
                                      Wayne, New Jersey 07470
                                      Please note: If you are a new customer, we can begin sharing your information 30 days from the
                                      date we sent this notice. When you are no longer our customer, we may continue to share your
                                      information as described in this notice. However, you can contact us at any time to limit our sharing.
                                      If you have any questions about this Privacy Policy Statement or about the security and
                                      confidentiality of your non-public personal information, please call the privacy representative in
           Questions?
                                      Customer Service at 800-522-4100. For calls made from outside of the U.S. and Canada, please call
                                      973-305-8800 or visit us at valley.com.

Who We Are
                                                     Valley companies that use “Valley National” or “VNB” in their names and Masters
Who is providing this notice?
                                                     Coverage Corporation.
What We Do
How does Valley protect my personal                  To protect your personal information from unauthorized access and use, we use security
information?                                         measures that comply with federal law. These measures include computer safeguards
                                                     and secured files and buildings. We permit only authorized employees trained in the
                                                     proper handling of customer information to access your information, and we require
                                                     companies that work for us to protect your information.
How does Valley collect my personal                  We collect your personal information, for example, when you:
information?                                         • open an account or apply for a loan
                                                     • pay your bills, make deposits or withdrawals from your account, use your
                                                        credit or debit card
                                                     We also collect your personal information from others, such as credit bureaus and
                                                     other companies.
Why can’t I limit all sharing?                       Federal law gives you the right to limit only:
                                                     • sharing for affiliates’ everyday business purposes—information about your
                                                        creditworthiness
                                                     • affiliates from using your information to market to you
                                                     • sharing for non-affiliates to market to you
What happens when I limit sharing for an
                                                     Your choices apply to everyone on your account.
account I hold jointly with someone else?
Definitions
Affiliates                                           Companies related by common ownership or control. They can be financial and
                                                     non-financial companies.
                                                     • Our affiliates include companies that use “Valley National” or ”VNB” in their
                                                        names and financial companies such as Masters Coverage Corp.
Non-Affiliates                                       Companies not related by common ownership or control. They can be financial and
                                                     non-financial companies.
                                                     • Valley does not share with non-affiliates so they can market to you.
Joint Marketing                                      A formal agreement between non-affiliated financial companies that together market
                                                     financial products or services to you.
                                                     • Our joint marketing partners include insurance and financial services companies.
Other Important Information
Valley will never ask for your personal account number or personal information via email. This Privacy Policy Statement is available
in all of our branches and also may be viewed on our website: valley.com. If you provide us with an e-mail address, we may use it to
contact you regarding your relationship with us, to advise you of our loan and deposit products, to provide you with information you
may have requested from us or to conduct business with Valley, including collection efforts, if necessary.
                             © 2019 Valley National Bank. Member FDIC. Equal Opportunity Lender. All Rights Reserved. VCS-8301
